<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Null Chapter</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Null Chapter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 13:20:48 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>STUXnet -- Just a virus?</title>
      <link>/blog/blog10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 13:20:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blog10/</guid>
      <description>STUXnet &amp;ndash; Just a virus? Well, let us investigate the past geopolitical scenarios first before diving into the topic. Early 1950s. Iran&amp;rsquo;s nuclear program beg an but in a slow state. The US supplied the Tehran Nuclear Research Centre (TNRC) with a small 5MWt research reactor fuelled by Highly Enriched Uranium (HEU) in 1967. In &amp;lsquo;73, the Shah unveiled ambitious plans to install 23,000Mwe of nuclear power in Iran by the end of the century, charging the newly founded Atomic Energy Organization of Iran (AEOI) with oversight of this task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptojacking</title>
      <link>/blog/blog9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 11:44:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blog9/</guid>
      <description>null_&#34;
What is Cryptojacking?
Cryptojacking is the unauthorized use of someone else’s computer to mine cryptocurrency. Hackers do this by either getting the victim to click on a malicious link through an email that loads cryptomining code on the
computer or by infecting a website with JavaScript code that auto -executes once loaded in the victim’s browser.
Either way, the cryptomining code then runs in the background as unsuspecting victims use their computers normally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web-Site Cookie</title>
      <link>/blog/blog8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 11:44:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blog8/</guid>
      <description>What is a Web-Site Cookie?
 Whenever we hear the word cookies the first thing that comes in our mind is text files with small piece of data like a username or password that are used to identify your computer as you use them and make your online experience easier and smooth. Data stored in a cookie is created by the server upon your connection. This data is labelled with an ID unique to you and your computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computing fears and hopes</title>
      <link>/blog/blog5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blog5/</guid>
      <description>The intricate relationships that humans have with the technologies they build are at the foundation of the creation of hacking as a societal problem. Technical advancement, a distinguishing feature of modernity, has created as many issues as it has solved problems. While computers and robots have been seen as providing respite from filthy, dangerous, and monotonous work for decades, they have also been viewed with some trepidation in terms of their potential to displace and even dominate humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Attack</title>
      <link>/blog/blog4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 02:55:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blog4/</guid>
      <description>If you are a cybersecurity expert living in today’s shark-infested cyber-world, your mission is to stay ahead of the bad guys and keep your activity safe. This starts by understanding your vulnerabilities, knowing the many ways by which your resistance can be breached, and then putting together in position the protections needed to maintain a secure, tough cybersecurity posture. It’s a big job and is significantly important to the security of your enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conflict or continuum?</title>
      <link>/blog/blog3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 02:52:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blog3/</guid>
      <description>Before talking about the beliefs and activities of digital technology aficionados who are also referred to as &amp;ldquo;hackers,&amp;rdquo; we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about how their defining activity has been framed as a social concern, and how that frame has been contested in many ways. The chapter finishes with several policy recommendations targeted at dealing with the more serious aspects of computer hacking.
Security threats are increasing at an exponential rate, having a significant impact on existing systems and the potential for severe repercussions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get started with WSL</title>
      <link>/blog/blog2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 21:54:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blog2/</guid>
      <description>Windows subsystem for Linux WSL is an optional feature of Windows 10 which allows the user to run Linux distributions natively on Windows10 without the use of a Virtual Machine. This tool is primarily used by developers and those who work on or with open source projects. You can access the windows file manager through the bash shell in Linux, and run shell scripts and GNU/Linux command-line applications including:
 Tools – vim, emacs Languages – Javascript/node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identify Which Website Sold Out Your Email ID</title>
      <link>/blog/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 16:23:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blog1/</guid>
      <description>Follow these simple steps to identify which company is selling your mail ID to spammers!
  Whenever you are registering yourself on any website you will receive a prompt to enter your email. While entering your mail id, do this simple hack:
  Add &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo; to your mail followed by the website name.
  Example: if your email id is admin@gmail.com you can register with admin+WebSiteName@gmail.com or admin+facebook@gmail.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
